<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StoryApp</string>

    <!-- Storing Title of the story into a array -->
    <string-array name="title_story">
        <item>An Old Man Lived in the Village</item>
        <item>The Wise Man</item>
        <item>The Foolish Donkey</item>
        <item>Having A Best Friend</item>
        <item>The Four Smart Students</item>
        <item>The Greedy Lion</item>
        <item>Two Friends and The Bear</item>
        <item>The Struggles of Our Life</item>
        <item>The Fox and The Grapes</item>
        <item>The Lion and The Poor Slave</item>
        <item>The Bogey Beast</item>
        <item>The Tortoise and the Hare</item>
        <item>The Tale of Johnny Town-Mouse</item>
        <item>The Night Train at Deoli</item>
        <item>There Will Come Soft Rains</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Storing Details of the story into a array -->
    <string-array name="details_story">
        <item>An old man lived in the village. He was one of the most unfortunate people in the
            world. The whole village was tired of him; he was always gloomy, he constantly
            complained and was always in a bad mood.The longer he lived, the more bile he was
            becoming and the more poisonous were his words. People avoided him, because his
            misfortune became contagious. It was even unnatural and insulting to be happy next to
            him.He created the feeling of unhappiness in others.But one day, when he turned eighty
            years old, an incredible thing happened. Instantly everyone started hearing the rumour:
“An Old Man is happy today, he doesn’t complain about anything, smiles, and even his face is
            freshened up.”The whole village gathered together. The old man was asked:Villager: What
            happened to you?“Nothing special. Eighty years I’ve been chasing happiness, and it was
            useless. And then I decided to live without happiness and just enjoy life. That’s why
            I’m happy now.” – An Old Man\n\n
         best friend slapped me in the face.”They kept on walking until they found an oasis,
            where they decided to take a bath. The one who had been slapped got stuck in the mire
            and started drowning, but the friend saved him. After he recovered from the near
            drowning, he wrote on a stone;“Today my best friend saved my life.”The friend who had
            slapped and saved his best friend asked him;“After I hurt you, you wrote in the
            sand and now, you write on a stone, why?”The other friend replied;“When someone hurts us
            we should write it down in sand where winds of forgiveness can erase it away. But, when
            someone does something good for us, we must engrave it in stone where no wind can ever
            erase it.”</item>

        <item>People have been coming to the wise man, complaining about the same problems every
            time. One day he told them a joke and everyone roared in laughter.After a couple of
            minutes, he told them the same joke and only a few of them smiled.When he told the same
            joke for the third time no one laughed anymore.The wise man smiled and said:“You can’t
            laugh at the same joke over and over. So why are you always crying about the same
            problem?”</item>

        <item>A salt seller used to carry the salt bag on his donkey to the market every day.On the
            way they had to cross a stream. One day the donkey suddenly tumbled down the stream and
            the salt bag also fell into the water. The salt dissolved in the water and hence the bag
            became very light to carry. The donkey was happy.Then the donkey started to play the
            same trick every day.The salt seller came to understand the trick and decided to teach a
            lesson to it. The next day he loaded a cotton bag on the donkey.Again it played the same
            trick hoping that the cotton bag would be still become lighter.But the dampened cotton
            became very heavy to carry and the donkey suffered. It learnt a lesson. It didn’t play
            the trick anymore after that day, and the seller was happy.</item>

        <item>A story tells that two friends were walking through the desert. During some point of
            the journey they had an argument, and one friend slapped the other one in the face.The
            one who got slapped was hurt, but without saying anything, wrote in the sand;“Today my
            best friend slapped me in the face.”They kept on walking until they found an oasis,
            where they decided to take a bath. The one who had been slapped got stuck in the mire
            and started drowning, but the friend saved him. After he recovered from the near
            drowning, he wrote on a stone;“Today my best friend saved my life.”The friend who had
            slapped and saved his best friend asked him;“After I hurt you, you wrote in the
            sand and now, you write on a stone, why?”The other friend replied;“When someone hurts us
            we should write it down in sand where winds of forgiveness can erase it away. But, when
            someone does something good for us, we must engrave it in stone where no wind can ever
            erase it.”</item>

        <item>One night four college students were out partying late night and didn’t study for the
            test which was scheduled for the next day. In the morning, they thought of a plan.They
            made themselves look dirty with grease and dirt.Then they went to the Dean and said they
            had gone out to a wedding last night and on their way back the tire of their car burst
            and they had to push the car all the way back. So they were in no condition to take the
            test.</item>

        <item>It was an incredibly hot day, and a lion was feeling very hungry.He came out of his
            den and searched here and there. He could find only a small hare. He caught the hare
            with some hesitation. “This hare can’t fill my stomach” thought the lion.</item>

        <item>Vijay and Raju were friends. On a holiday they went walking into a forest, enjoying
            the beauty of nature. Suddenly they saw a bear coming at them. They became frightened.
            Raju, who knew all about climbing trees, ran up to a tree and climbed up quickly.
            He didn’t think of Vijay. Vijay had no idea how to climb the tree.Vijay thought for a
            second. He’d heard animals don’t prefer dead bodies, so he fell to the ground and held
            his breath. The bear sniffed him and thought he was dead. So, it went on its way.</item>

        <item>Once upon a time a daughter complained to her father that her life was miserable and
            that she didn’t know how she was going to make it.She was tired of fighting and
            struggling all the time. It seemed just as one problem was solved, another one soon
            followed.Her father, a chef, took her to the kitchen. He filled three pots with water
            and placed each on a high fire.Once the three pots began to boil, he placed potatoes in
            one pot, eggs in the second pot and ground coffee beans in the third pot. He then let
            them sit and boil, without saying a word to his daughter.The daughter, moaned and
            impatiently waited, wondering what he was doing. After twenty minutes he turned off the
            burners.</item>

        <item>Taking a few steps back, the fox jumped and just missed the hanging grapes. Again the
            fox took a few paces back and tried to reach them but still failed.Finally, giving up,
            the fox turned up his nose and said, “They’re probably sour anyway,” and proceeded to
            walk away.</item>

        <item>A slave, ill-treated by his master, runs away to the forest. There he comes across a
            lion in pain because of a thorn in his paw. The slave bravely goes forward and removes
            the thorn gently.The lion without hurting him goes away.Some days later, the slave’s
            master comes hunting to the forest and catches many animals and cages them. The slave
            is spotted by the masters’ men who catch him and bring him to the cruel master.The
            master asks for the slave to be thrown into the lion’s cage.The slave is awaiting his
            death in the cage when he realizes that it is the same lion that he had helped.
            The slave rescued the lion and all other caged animals.</item>

        <item>A woman finds a pot of treasure on the road while she is returning from work.
            Delighted with her luck, she decides to keep it. As she is taking it home, it keeps
            changing. However, her enthusiasm refuses to fade away.What Is Great About It: The old
            lady in this story is one of the most cheerful characters anyone can encounter in
            English fiction. Her positive disposition (personality) tries to make every negative
            transformation seem like a gift, and she helps us look at luck as a matter of
            perspective rather than events.</item>

        <item>This classic fable tells the story of a very slow tortoise (another word for turtle)
            and a speedy hare (another word for rabbit). The tortoise challenges the hare to a race.
            The hare laughs at the idea that a tortoise could run faster than him, but when the two
            actually race, the results are surprising.What Is Great About It: Have you ever heard
            the English expression, “Slow and steady wins the race”? This story is the basis for
            that common phrase. This timeless short story teaches a lesson that we all know but can
            sometimes forget: Natural talent is no substitute for hard work, and overconfidence
            often leads to failure.This short story is available on FluentU, so you can take
            advantages of all of FluentU’s great language-learning features while revisiting this
            childhood classic.</item>

        <item>Timmie Willie is a country mouse who is accidentally transported to a city in a
            vegetable basket. When he wakes up, he finds himself in a party and makes a friend.
            When he is unable to bear the city life, he returns to his home but invites his friend
            to the village. When his friend visits him, something similar happens.What Is Great
            About It: Humans have been living without cities or villages for most of history. That
            means that both village and city life are recent inventions. And just like every other
            invention, we need to decide their costs and benefits.The story is precisely about this
            debate. It is divided into short paragraphs and has illustrations for each scene. This
            is best for beginners who want to start reading immediately.</item>

        <item>Ruskin Bond used to spend his summer at his grandmother’s house in Dehradun. While
            taking the train, he always had to pass through a small station called Deoli. No one
            used to get down at the station and nothing happened there. Until one day he sees a
            girl selling fruit and he is unable to forget her.What Is Great About It: Ruskin Bond is
            a writer who can communicate deep feelings in a simple way. This story is about our
            attachment to strangers and why we cherish them even though we do not meet them ever
            again.</item>

        <item>Earth has been destroyed by war and no one lives on it anymore. The robots and the
            machines continue to function and serve human beings who have long ago died.What Is
            Great About It: The title is taken from a poem that describes how nature will continue
            its work long after humanity is gone. But in this story, we see that nature plays a
            supporting role and the machines are the ones who have taken its place.They continue
            their work without any human or natural assistance. This shows how technology has
            replaced nature in our lives and how it can both destroy us and carry on without
            humanity itself.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
